DEVON UNDERHILL

UNITED STATES NAVY DIVER

Navy salvage diver with 5 years of experience, responsible for managing \$2.3 million of gear and equipment while deployed to Djibouti, Africa on national level tasking. Computer science graduate student at Old Dominion University since 2023, working as a member of the Center for Real Time Computing the study of quantum computing. Chemical engineering graduate published as second author on research detailing the use of organic acids for inhibiting phase change of catalyst support.

SKILLS

- C++, Python, MATLAB, Excel
- Critical thinking
- Strong organizational and leadership skills
- Experienced independent researcher

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Masters of Science

Old Dominion University | 2023 - Present

CHEMICAL ENGINEERING

Bachelor of Science

University of Colorado | 2012 - 2017

EXPERIENCE

GRADUATE RESEARCHER

Old Dominion University 2023 - Present

Ongoing research into the application of quantum computing algorithms to traditional computer science problems in order to achieve significant speedup. Focused on implementation of quantum algorithms in the machine learning space.

NAVY DIVER

2019 - Present

Completed national level tasking deployment to Djibouti, Africa. Works on the implementation of critical training curriculum for expeditionary Navy Diver units enabling successful deployments around the world.

CONTACT

devon.underhill45@gmail.com devonunderhill.github.io